DARIA SIDORKO

206.354.6975 A daria.sidorko@gmail.com www.dariasidorko.com

Creative front end web development professional with experience in building and maintaining websites. Quick learner and effective team member with excellent technical and communicative skills, with strong passion for innovative and fresh ideas as well as well thought through, well designed products.

EDUCATION

Sep 2014 - Present IT APPLICATIONS DEVELOPMENT, AAS

Lake Washington Institute of Technology | Kirkland, WA

two consecutive quarters on the Dean's list and one quarter on the President's list

May 2013 ARCHITECTURAL DESIGN STUDIES, BS

Washington State University | Pullman, WA

SKILLS

TECHNICAL: CSS, HTML5, JavaScript, JQuery, SQL, C++, Object-oriented programming

TOOLS: Wordpress, Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Axure, Bootstrap, Balsamig

DESIGN: Sketching, Wireframing, Interaction Design

EXPERIENCE

Jan 2016 - Present FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance | Bellevue, WA

- Designing, developing and maintaining responsive websites using various platforms and frameworks.
- Creating custom responsive themes with such tools as Wordpress or Bootstrap framework.

Aug 2016 - Sep 2016 DESIGNER | WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

Univera Inc I Seattle, WA



- Responsible for the design and front-end implementation of the responsive website for the world's largest grower and processor of Aloe Vera.
- The development of a new front-end included all HTML, CSS, integration of Bootstrap responsive grid on the Wordpress platform.

May 2016 - July 2016 VISUAL DATA SPECIALIST

Google | Bothell, WA - Contract through Randstad



- Was responsible for Data Labeling & Quality Assurance for Google Self-Driven car project using proprietary software and tools.
- Analyzed data and made decisions based on policies as set by quality control.
- Adapted to quick task changes as the project focus progresses.
- Delivered projects on aggressive deadlines.
- Worked alongside engineers, providing feedback to improve proprietary software.

Sep 2013 - Nov 2016 PROPERTY MANAGER

WALL Wilson Management, Inc.

Wilson Management Inc | Bellevue, WA

- Maintained an average of ninety percent occupancy rate over the course of three years.
- Increased property income by thirty percent by raising rent.
- Handled all paperwork, including the processing of applications according to company policy, handling of written service requests from residents, maintaining tenant files and kept reporting records, issued and distributed all other legal notices as required.

-Handled all rent collections, rent deposits, turnover and leasing of all vacant units in timely manner.

June 2015 - Dec 2015 TUTOR FOR IT AND APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

Lake Washington Institute of Technology | Kirkland, WA

Tutoring students for software and applications development courses.

